{
    "subject": "Meir_Zarchi",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Camille_Keaton",
    "human_readable": "Meir Zarchi is married to Camille Keaton.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.910866916179657,
            "question": "Who is Meir Zarchi married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9053255319595337,
            "question": "To whom is Camille Keaton married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8901564478874207,
            "question": "Who is Camille Keaton married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8868826627731323,
            "question": "Is Camille Keaton married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6945923566818237,
            "question": "What is the name of Meir Zarchi's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6638318300247192,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Camille Keaton?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.660807728767395,
            "question": "Can you tell me the names of Meir Zarchi and his spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6597349643707275,
            "question": "Is Meir Zarchi in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4953612685203552,
            "question": "What is the name of Meir Zarchi's partner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1957494020462036,
            "question": "Who are the individuals involved in this marriage?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Meir Zarchi is married to Camille Keaton.",
            "html": "yago_30169_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Meir Zarchi's partner?",
            "html": "yago_30169_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Meir Zarchi in a relationship?",
            "html": "yago_30169_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me the names of Meir Zarchi and his spouse?",
            "html": "yago_30169_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30169_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30169_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30169_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30169_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30169_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30169_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30169_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30169_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30169_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30169_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Meir Zarchi and Camille Keaton were married for 3 years, from 1979 to 1982."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Meir Zarchi is married to Camille Keaton.\" Specifically, multiple documents mention their marriage:\n\n- \"Camille Keaton was previously married to Sidney Luft and Meir Zarchi (1979 - 1982).\"\n- \"Meir Zarchi and Camille Keaton were married for 3 years. They dated for 1 year after getting together in 1978 and married in 1979. 3 years later they divorced in 1982.\"\n\nThese details confirm their marital relationship, making the statement correct according to the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}